Guide to the George Mason University Office of the President records, 1949-2004
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 3: Lorin A. Thompson, 1964-1975, (17.5 boxes)
  - Houston vs. Krug and Thompson, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Johnson, Sandra - Jones Case, re: Broadside, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Krug, commencement, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Land acquisition, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Land deed ceremony, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Latin American students, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Legislative tour of George Mason College of the University of Virginia, December 7, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Letter to faculty and staff about construction schedule of a new parking lot, November 1970 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Library dedication, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Lists for library ground breaking, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Long range planning committee, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Low cost building - Student Center building, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Mallory House incident December, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Manual of the Board of Visitors of University of Virginia, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Master plan, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Master plan, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Meetings, Re: Black recruitment, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Memos: Lorin Thompson [1 of 2], 1966-1973 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Memos: Lorin Thompson [2 of 2], 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Mrs. Elliott, GMU beautification vs. construction, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - News releases, 1965-1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Newsclippings and articles On student unrest, 1969-1971 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Non-credit courses, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - North Building, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Office of Institutional Analysis, 1969-1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - The Patriot, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Personnel: Salary ranges, 1966-1973 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of Dr. Thompson and Thompson Hall, undated-1999 (Box 16)
  - Physical education building ground breaking, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Physical education building, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Planning Office, Sensbach, 1968, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Policy: Administrative, backgrounds materials, general correspondence University of Virginia and George Mason College, 1964-1970 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Policy: Administrative, backgrounds materials, general correspondence University of Virginia and George Mason College, 1971-1976 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - President Shannon, 1967-1971 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - President Shannon [1 of 2], 1959-1967 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - President Shannon [2 of 2], 1959-1967 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Print exhibition at Newcomb Hall, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Lorin Thompson's profile, 1970-1972 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Promotion of faculty members in rank, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Provost's Office, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Provost's Office, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Report on summer sessions [1 of 2], 1966-1974 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Report on summer sessions [2 of 2], 1966-1974 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Renewals and non-renewals of terms of faculty members, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Dr. Thompson scrapbooks, 1969-1971 (Box 18)
  - Dr. Thompson scrapbooks, 1965-1969 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Thompson scrapbooks, 1970-1975 (Box 20)
  - Scholarship committee, 1969-1972 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Sessions planning committee, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Shea, James M. Jr, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Space requirements, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Staff awards committee, June 20, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Financial aid, 1970-1972 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia: H.E.W, 1969-1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Statement for 1972 General Assembly, history of George Mason University (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Student affairs, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Student assembly, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Student, teacher, and course evaluation of the faculty, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Student government, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Student housing committee, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Student organizations, 1969-1975 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Student problems, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Student rights, conducts, responsibilities, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Student teaching at GMU, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Student unrest, May 1970 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Summer session, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Tallwood, 1968-1970 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Teacher education committee, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Title VI: H.E.W. Compliance, visit, October 7-9, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Trailers for George Mason University, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - United States Commission on Civil Rights [1 of 2], 1971 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - United States Commission on Civil Rights [2 of 2], 1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - University expansion, 1964-1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Includes slides
  - University of Virginia Center for Continuing Education, 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - University of Virginia history, circa 1967 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Upward Bound program at George Mason College, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Draft-dodging Vietnam, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - John Carl Warnecke & Associates, 1967-1975 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Series 4: Vergil H. Dykstra, 1962-1980, (6 boxes)
  Series four, "Vergil H. Dykstra", with papers dating from 1962 to 1980, focuses on the years Dykstra served as president of George Mason University from 1973 to 1977. This series includes budget reports, a Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) report, State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) papers, building plans, and documents from the University Center in Virginia, Inc.
  - Administrative performance review evaluation forms, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Admissions Office: Grievance, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Affirmative Action: Employment discrimination charges, 1973-1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Bicentennial, 1973-1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Budget Biennium, 1974-1976 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Budget Biennium [1 of 2], 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Budget Biennium [2 of 2], 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Budget Biennium [1 of 2], 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Budget Biennium [2 of 2], 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Budget: Capital outlay, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Budget: Comprehensive fee, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Budget expenditure listing, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Budget expenditure listing, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Six year expenditure plan, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Budget: Faculty salaries, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Budget: Faculty salaries, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Budget: Faculty salaries, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Budget: M & O, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Budget: Memos to Vice President Adams, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Committee on faculty and academic standards, May 1972-April 1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Committee on faculty and academic standards, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Committee on faculty and academic standards, 1977-1979 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Consortium: Public hearing, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Consortium: Public hearing, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Audrey Moore correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Dean for Student Affairs, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Dedication of Robinson Hall, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Evening session, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Facilities Planning: Student housing I, 1973-1978 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - General faculty meetings and minutes, 1973-1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - George Mason University Foundation: Fairfax High School, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - The George Mason University student, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - The Graduate advisory committee (visit, report, and related correspondence), October 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Graduate school, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Holiday schedule, 1972-1976 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Investigation of George Mason University athletic financial aid, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Library, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - National Secretaries Association, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Neighbourhood Youth Corps, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Nellie Dykstra Memorial Library Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Questionnaires and reports: Miscellaneous, 1967-1976 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Registration and profile of entering class, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Schedule of classes, Spring 1974 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Shaner Report, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Graduate follow-up report due Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS), September 1, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) graduate program report, September 1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Spring commencement, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Staff meeting: Vice President for Academic Affairs, July 1, 1975- June 1976 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Letters of intent and degree proposals, 1972-1976 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Student affairs: Student government conflict with Broadside, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Student enrollment, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Sullivan, John P.: Director, Office of Institutional Analysis, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Sullivan, John P.: Director, Office of Institutional Analysis, 1970-1975 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Summer session survey and results, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Textbooks authored by George Mason University faculty, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - University Center in Virginia, Inc., 1962-1973 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - University Center in Virginia, Inc., 1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - University Center in Virginia, Inc., 1975 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - University research typing service, 1974-1976 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Winter commencement, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Series 5: Robert C. Krug, 1977-1978, (1.5 boxes)
  Series five, "Robert C. Krug, 1977-1978", focuses on Dr. Krug's tenure as president during 1977-1978. Included in this series is correspondence, Dr. Krug's memoranda, documents on campus security officers and the 1977 bond referendum.
  - Bond referendum, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Concerning the arming of the campus security officers, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence [1 of 2], 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence [2 of 2], 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Housing I: Sherman vs. GMU, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Invitation for luncheon post commencement ceremony, January 1978 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Dr. Robert C. Krug memo's, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Dr. Robert C. Krug memo's, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Office of the Governor, January 1978 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Series 6: George W. Johnson, 1957-2004, (78 boxes)
  Series six, "George W. Johnson", with materials dating from 1957 to 2004, is the largest series in this collection. George W. Johnson was president from 1979 to 1996 and successfully guided George Mason University from a small liberal arts college into a major university. Included in this series are facilities and education plans for expansion in Arlington and Prince William, articles and notes collected by Johnson, documents on athletics, Board of Visitors meeting minutes, daily calendars, documents on the campus police, correspondence, documents concerning Larry Czarda, correspondence with various state departments, facilities planning papers, the Faculty Senate meeting minutes, Governor's files, documents on Johnson's inauguration, memoranda, Office of the Attorney General correspondence, newsclippings, Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) self-study, speeches, as well as documents from the State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV), University life, and the Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC). Photographs, scrapbooks, and the George Mason stamp are also present in this series.
  - A letter from the President, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Admissions activity, 1989-1990 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Advisory committee on girls' education, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Affirmative action salary analysis, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Arlington campus background information (for AGM), 1995-1996 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Alumni survey 1992 graduates, Fall 1995 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - American council on education, 1995-1996 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - American council on higher education, B.H.E. forum, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - An academic plan 1978-1988, October 1, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - ARCH III and landmark dedication, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Advanced studies center in Arlington, June 14, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Arlington campus: "A program for an educating community", December 1988 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Arlington campus facilities planning, 1986-1995 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Arlington campus future parking strategies, April 1994 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Arlington campus report, December 1988 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Arlington economic future committee, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Arlington joint committee, 1988-1996 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Arlington office of economic development, 1988-1992 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Arlington: Survey of exterior walls for Metro Center, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Art in public places, 1989-1993 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Articles and notes, February 10, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Articles and notes, September 17, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Articles and notes, circa 1988 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Articles and notes: Briefing paper, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Articles and notes: Broadside orientation issue, April 3, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Articles and notes: Discussion on Banks and the hi tech industry, January 28, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Articles and notes: Gazette, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Articles and notes: General faculty, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Articles and notes: GMU progress, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Articles and notes: GMU salaries and cost of living, January 29, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Articles and notes: Greater Washington board of trade outlook, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Articles and notes: "Habbit of the heart", undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Articles and notes: Higher education, business, industry, undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Articles and notes: Organizational issues, February 13, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Articles and notes: Outline faculty state of University address, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Articles and notes: The President's game, undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Articles and notes: State government news, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Articles and notes: University brochure "Growing into the future", undated (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Articles and notes: University Day, April 7, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Arts explosion, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Arts gala, heritage quilt cards, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Assessing user impact in the library community, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Athletics article: "Light and shadows on college athletics", December 1990 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Athletics: Enrollment, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Athletics: NCAA site visit, 1993-1995 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Audit and review commission, 1993-1997 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Auditor of public accounts, 1991-1996 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Beyond boundaries: Transforming the University, circa 1990 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - "Bigotry on campus", American Jewish committee, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Black American women articles, undated (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Board of Visitors (BOV) briefing (NVRT), 1995-1996 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Board of Visitors (BOV) meeting reports [1 of 2], 1990-1996 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Board of Visitors (BOV) meeting reports [2 of 2], 1987-1990 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Board of Visitors (BOV) minutes, September 15, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Board of Visitiors (BOV) update reports, 1991-1996 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Bomb threat procedure, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Broadside papers (Mason Gazette), 1983-1986 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Budget, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Budget 1-61111 external affairs, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    See also 37.5
  - Budget 1-61111 external affairs, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Building fire codes, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Calendar: Day at a glance, 1969 (Box 33)
  - Calendar: Day at a glance, 1970 (Box 33)
  - Calendar: Day at a glance, 1970 (Box 33)
  - Calendar: Daily minder, "BB", 1971 (Box 33)
  - Calendar: Daily minder, "GWJ", 1971 (Box 33)
  - Calendar: Daily minder, "GWJ", 1972 (Box 33)
  - Calendar: Daily minder, "BLB", 1972 (Box 33)
  - Calendar: Daily minder, "B. L. Breese CLA", 1973 (Box 33)
  - Calendar: Daily minder, "G. W. Johnson CLA", 1973 (Box 33)
  - Calendar: Daily minder, "B. L. Breese CLA", 1974 (Box 33)
  - Calendar: Daily minder, "G. W. Johnson CLA", 1974 (Box 34)
  - Calendar: Day minder, 1975 (Box 34)
  - Calendar: Day minder, "Beverly. L. Breese, CLA", 1976 (Box 34)
  - Calendar: Day minder, 1977 (Box 34)
  - Campus civility, 1990-1992 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Campus civility: "Racism on campus part II" (synthesis), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Campus civility: Secretary Dyke speech, June 6, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Campus police: "The campus law enforcement administrator", 1982 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Campus police: Crime reports, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Campus police: Escort service procedure manual, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Campus police: George Mason University disaster plan, July 1, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Campus police miscellaneous, 1992-1996 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Candidates letter (draft), 1971 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Center for advanced studies (UVA) with comparison research institutes, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Center for innovative technology, 1984-1991 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Center for innovative technology, 1986-1992 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Virginia's center for innovative technology, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Center for innovative technology details of operating budget for fiscal year 1993, circa 1992 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Chichester commission report (draft), December 7, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - College of Arts and Sciences (CAS): Dean's budget recommendation summaries, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - College of Arts and Sciences (CAS): Meetings and minutes, 1989-1994 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - College of Education and Human Services, five year plan, 1985-1993 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Committee on accreditation, psychology, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Committees, nomination, 1988-1991 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Communications infrastructure, October 12, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Community College system, 1981-1991 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Community outreach, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Computing and information systems, five year plan, 1991-1996 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Conflict of interests, Richmond, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Conflict of interests, Richmond, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, July 6, 1979-November 18, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, December 21, 1982-March 29, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Admissions, November 10, 1987-July 21, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Affirmative action, minority statistics, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Athletics, NCAA, 1995-1996 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Attorney general: Stone vs. University of Maryland, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Attorney general, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Board of visitors (BOV), May 7, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Board of visitors (BOV), July 23, 1985-March 4, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Board of visitors (BOV), March 27, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Board of visitors (BOV), budget 1-61111 external affairs, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Business, Joseph L. Fisher [1 of 8], December 1986-March 1988 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Business, Joseph L. Fisher [2 of 8], December 1986-March 1988 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Business, Joseph L. Fisher [3 of 8], December 1986-March 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Business, Joseph L. Fisher [4 of 8], December 1986-March 1988 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Business, Joseph L. Fisher [5 of 8], December 1986-March 1988 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Business, Joseph L. Fisher [6 of 8], December 1986-March 1988 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Business, Joseph L. Fisher [7 of 8], December 1986-March 1988 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Business, Joseph L. Fisher [8 of 8], December 1986-March 1988 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Business, Joseph L. Fisher and Ken Murphy, February 10, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Business higher education forum, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Business higher education forum, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Business higher education forum, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Business higher education forum, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Business higher education forum, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Business higher education forum, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Business higher education forum, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Business higher education forum, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Business higher education forum, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Capital outlay tour final, September 9, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Captial outlay task force, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Centers and institutes, 1987-1994 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Centers and institutes: The American Center for Strategic Studies, undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April-August 1978 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, September-December 1978 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, January-December 1979 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, January-May 1980 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, June-September 1980 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, October-December 1980 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, January-February 1981 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, March-May 1981 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, June-August 1981 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, September-December 1981 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April-December 1982 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, September 1982 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, October 1982 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, November 1982 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, December 1982 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, January 1983 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, February 1983 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, March 1983 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April 1983 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, May 1983 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, June 1983 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, July 1983 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, August 1983 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, September 1983 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, October 1983 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, November 1983 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, December 1983 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, January 1984 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, February 1984 (Box 42, Folder 6)